A Guide to the Island Resources Foundation records FA1200
Rockefeller Archive Center
- General Correspondence, 1962, 1964, 1967-2016; 4; 13.67 Cubic Feet 36 letter document boxes
  - Mukti Fund, 1986-1987, 1992-1996, 1998-2005 (Box 173, Folder 2011)
  - Museum Association of the Caribbean (MAC), 1989-1999, 2001-2004, 2012 (Box 173, Folder 2012)
  - "N" Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1986, 1988-1995, 1997-1998, 2000, 2003-2004 (Box 173, Folder 2013)
  - National Academy of Sciences, 1981-1983, 1985-1986, 1988-1989, 1991 (Box 174, Folder 2014)
  - National Fish and Wildlife Foundation, 1993, 1997-1998, 2001 (Box 174, Folder 2015)
  - National Parks and Conservation Association, 1981-1984 (Box 174, Folder 2016)
  - National Resources Defense Council, Inc., 1976-1981, 1985 (Box 174, Folder 2017)
  - Natural Resources Institute, 1997, 2001 (Box 174, Folder 2018)
  - The Nature Conservancy, Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1976-1977, 1979-1981, 1984-2004, 2006, 2010 (Box 174, Folder 2019)
  - The Nature Conservancy, Estate Little Princess, 1970, 1977, 1979, 1982 (Box 174, Folder 2020)
  - The Nature Conservancy, International Program, Caribbean Program, 1987, 1990, 1993-1995, 1997, 1999-2007, 2011, 2013-2014 (Box 174, Folder 2021)
  - The Nature Conservancy, Virgin Islands Program, 1992-2002, 2004, 2006, 2015 (Box 174, Folder 2022)
  - Netherlands Antilles, 1974, 1977, 1980, 1983, 1986, 1993-1996, 1998-2002 (Box 174, Folder 2023)
  - Nichols, Maynard, 1980-1983, 1985-1986, 1989, 1995-1997, 1999-2000, 2003 (Box 175, Folder 2024)
  - Nunn, Thomas, 1980-1985, 2008 (Box 175, Folder 2025)
  - "O" Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1986-1987, 1989, 1991-1992, 1995-1996, 1998-2000 (Box 175, Folder 2026)
  - Ocean Conservancy, Formerly Center for Marine Conservation (CMC), 1982, 1984, 1986-1987, 1991, 1993, 1995, 1997-2005, 2007-2008 (Box 175, Folder 2027)
  - Olsen, James and Mary Anne, 1980-1981, 1983 (Box 175, Folder 2028)
  - O'Neal, Michael, 1989-1990, 1999, 2005, 2008-2012, 2014 (Box 175, Folder 2029)
  - Organization for Cooperation in Overseas Development, 1999-2000 (Box 175, Folder 2030)
  - Organization of American States, 1972, 1974-1977, 1979-1983, 1986-1990, 1992-1995, 1997-2000 (Box 175, Folder 2031)
  - Organization of American States, Information, 1988, 1994 (Box 175, Folder 2032)
  - Organization of Eastern Caribbean States, 1986-1991, 1993-1996, 1998-2000, 2002-2010, 2012, 2014 (Box 176, Folder 2033-2034)
  - "P" Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1986-1994, 1996, 1998-2000, 2002 (Box 176, Folder 2035)
  - Pan American Development Foundation, 1982-1984, 1986-1990 (Box 176, Folder 2036)
  - Pan American Health Organization (PAHO), 1980-1982, 1984-1988, 1990-1994 (Box 176, Folder 2037)
  - The Panos Institute, 1987-1990, 1995, 1997-1999, 2005-2006, 2010-2011, 2013 (Box 176, Folder 2038)
  - Partners for Livable Places, 1984-1995, 2001 (Box 176, Folder 2039)
  - Potter, Bruce, 1979-1989, 1992-1995, 1998-1999, 2001 (Box 176, Folder 2040)
  - Pulispher, Lydia, 1980-1989, 1991, 1994-1995, 1997, 1999-2000 (Box 177, Folder 2041)
  - Putney, Allen, 1977-1992, 1996 (Box 177, Folder 2042)
  - "Q" Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1990, 1993, 1998 (Box 177, Folder 2043)
  - "R" Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1986-1992, 1995-1998, 2000-2003, 2006 (Box 177, Folder 2044)
  - Ragster, La Verne, 1997-1999, 2002-20003, 2007-2009 (Box 177, Folder 2045)
  - Rainey, William, 1974-1977, 1979-1989, 1991-1993, 1995-1998, 2002-2003, 2005, 2007 (Box 177, Folder 2046)
  - RARE Center for Tropical Conservation, 1989-1999, 2001, 2005 (Box 177, Folder 2047-2048)
  - Renard, Yves and Tighe Geoghegan, 1977, 1980, 1982-1994, 1996, 1999-2000 (Box 177, Folder 2049)
  - Rockefeller Brothers Fund, Development Support Grant, 1978-1981 (Box 178, Folder 2050)
  - Rockefeller Brothers Fund, William S. Moody, 1974-1976, 1978-1989, 1991-1994, 1996-1997, 1999, 2002, 2006-2008, 2014-2015 (Box 178, Folder 2051-2052)
  - Rockefeller Foundation, 1989-1991 (Box 178, Folder 2053)
  - Rockefeller, Laurance S., 1971-1973, 1975, 1979, 198, 1986, 1988, 1992, 1996, 2002-2004, 2006-2012, 2014-2015 (Box 178, Folder 2054)
  - Rockresorts, Inc., 1973, 1975, 1977 (Box 178, Folder 2055)
  - Royal Society for the Protection of Birds (RSPB), 1997-1999, 2001, 2010 (Box 178, Folder 2056)
  - "S" Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1990-2002, 2005 (Box 178, Folder 2058)
  - Salvat, Bernard, 1976-1977, 1979-1981 (Box 178, Folder 2059)
  - Scholarly Resources Inc., 1977-1979, 1982 (Box 178, Folder 2060)
  - Schurer, Nathaniel, 1979-1982, 1985, 1988, 1990 (Box 178, Folder 2061)
  - SIDSNET, Information, 1998-1999, 2010 (Box 178, Folder 2062)
  - Skerritt, Richard, 1982-1983, 1986, 2004-2005, 2009 (Box 178, Folder 2063)
  - Smithsonian Institution, Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1973-1979, 1985-1990, 1990 (Box 179, Folder 2064)
  - Smithsonian Institution, Fosberg, F. Raymond, 1972-1974, 1976-1977, 1979, 1985-1986 (Box 179, Folder 2065)
  - Society for the Conservation and Study of Caribbean Birds (SCSCB), 1989, 1996, 2003-2004, 2006, 2009, 2011-2013 (Box 179, Folder 2066)
  - Sorgeloos, Patrick, 1980, 1982, 1985, 1988 (Box 179, Folder 2067)
  - South Pacific Islands, 1974-1977, 1981-1982, 1985-1986, 1989 (Box 179, Folder 2068)
  - South Pacific Commission, 1972, 1974, 1977, 1980-1981, 1983-1984, 1986-1988, 1992-1993 (Box 179, Folder 2070)
  - Spinard, Bernard, 1994-1998, 2000-2001 (Box 179, Folder 2070)
  - St. Croix Environmental Association (SEA), 1998-2000 (Box 179, Folder 2072)
  - St. George's University, Grenada, Institute for Caribbean and International Studies, 2000-2001 (Box 179, Folder 2073)
  - St. Kitts, 1971-1972, 1974-1977, 1980-1982, 1985-1989, 1991, 1996-1997, 2000-2002 (Box 179, Folder 2074)
  - St. Kitts and Nevis, Correspondence with the Government, 1970, 1972-1974, 1978-1980, 1980, 1984-1989, 1993, 1995, 1998, 2000-2001 (Box 179, Folder 2075)
  - St. Lucia, 1972-1974, 1977-1978, 1980, 1983, 1990, 1992, 1995, 1998 (Box 179, Folder 2076)
  - St. Lucia, Archaeological and Historical Society and National Trust, 1972-1978, 1980, 1984-1986, 1988, 1991, 1998 (Box 179, Folder 2077)
  - St. Lucia, Correspondence with Government, 1969, 1973-1974, 1978, 1980-1988, 1994-1995, 1999, 2002-2005 (Box 179, Folder 2078)
  - St. Lucia, National Research and Development Foundation (NRDF), 1978, 1986 (Box 179, Folder 2079)
  - St. Vincent, 1973, 1976, 1979, 1981, 1988, 1990, 2007 (Box 180, Folder 2080)
  - St. Vincent, Correspondence with Government, 1980, 1987-1989, 1995 (Box 180, Folder 2081)
  - St. Vincent National Trust, 1974-1975, 1978 (Box 180, Folder 2082)
  - "T" Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1980-1988, 1992-1994, 1996-1998, 2001 (Box 180, Folder 2083)
  - Thompson, Terrence, Envirosphere, 1983-1989 (Box 180, Folder 2084)
  - Thorsell, James, 1980-1984, 1992 (Box 180, Folder 2085)
  - Trinidad and Tobago, Government Correspondence, 1972-1973, 1975-1978, 1980-1981, 1988, 1991, 1995-1996, 1998, 2002-2003 (Box 180, Folder 2086)
  - Trinidad and Tobago, Chaguaramas Development Authority, 1976-1977 (Box 180, Folder 2087)
  - Trinidad and Tobago, Trinidad and Tobago National Commission for UNESCO, 1978 (Box 180, Folder 2088)
  - Tropical Development and Research Institute, 1978 (Box 180, Folder 2089)
  - Trust Territories, 1970, 1972-1977, 1982, 1984-1985, 1987 (Box 180, Folder 2090)
  - Turks and Caicos, 1973-1976, 1980, 1988, 1990, 1996, 2002, 2006 (Box 180, Folder 2091)
  - "U" Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1982, 1988, 1990 (Box 180, Folder 2092)
  - United Kingdom Overseas Territories Conservation Forum, 1991-1997, 1999, 2001, 2012-2014 (Box 180, Folder 2093)
  - United Kingdom Overseas Territories Conservation Forum, Wider Caribbean Working Group, 2013-2016 (Box 180, Folder 2094)
  - United Nations (UN) Conference on Trade and Development (UNCTD), 1985-1987 (Box 180, Folder 2095)
  - United Nations (UN) Development Programme (UNDP), 1974-1975, 1980-1982, 1986, 1989-1990, 1993-2001 (Box 180, Folder 2096)
  - United Nations (UN) /Economic Commission for Latin America and the Caribbean (ECLAC), 1986-1989, 1991, 1993-1999, 2001 (Box 181, Folder 2097-2098)
  - United Nations (UN) Environmental Programme (UNEP), 1978, 1981, 1983, 1986-1989, 1993, 1995-1996, 1998, 2001-2002, 2004, 2006-2007, 2010 (Box 181, Folder 2099)
  - United Nations (UN) Environmental Programme (UNEP), Caribbean Program Correspondence, 1975-1977, 1980, 1984, 1986, 1988-2001, 2004, 2006-2007 (Box 181, Folder 2100)
  - United Nations (UN) Environmental Programme (UNEP)/CEPNET, 1995, 1997-1999 (Box 181, Folder 2101)
  - United Nations (UN)/FAO (Food and Agriculture Organization of the UN), 1972-1975, 1986, 1989-1991, 1994-1995, 1998, 2002 (Box 181, Folder 2102)
  - United Nations (UN)/UNESCO, 1973, 1977-1978, 1980, 1983-1989, 1996, 2002 (Box 181, Folder 2103)
  - UNESCO/Division of Ecological Sciences, Environment and Development in Coastal Regular and Small Islands, 1981-1983, 1985-1986, 1988-1990, 1992-1993, 1996-1997, 200-2002, 2009 (Box 181, Folder 2104)
  - UNESCO/Intergovernmental Oceanographic Commission (IOC) and IOC/IOCARIBE, 1995-1999, 2002 (Box 181, Folder 2105)
  - US Government, Congress of the United States, Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1982, 1984-1987, 1989 (Box 181, Folder 2106)
  - US Government, Congress of the United States, Office of Technology Assessment, 1982-1985, 1987-1989, 1993, 1995 (Box 182, Folder 2107)
  - US Government, Congress of the United States, Office of Technology Assessment, Insular Areas Study, 1983-1987 (Box 182, Folder 2108)
  - US Government, Congress of the United States, Virgin Islands Delegation to Congress, 1981-1985, 1987, 1989, 1997 (Box 182, Folder 2109)
  - US Government, Department of Agriculture, Forest Service, 1989, 1994-1995, 1999-2002 (Box 182, Folder 2110)
  - US Government, Department of the Army Corps of Engineers, 1982-1983, 1985, 1990, 1993, 1996 (Box 182, Folder 2111)
  - US Government, Department of Commerce, National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration (NOAA), 1981-1983, 1985-1989, 1993-1995, 1997-2000, 2002-2004, 2007 (Box 182, Folder 2112)
  - US Government, Department of Commerce, National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration (NOAA), International Office, 1993-1995, 2002 (Box 182, Folder 2113)
  - US Government, Department of Commerce, National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration (NOAA), National Marine Fisheries Service, 1984, 1986 (Box 182, Folder 2114)
  - US Government, Department of Commerce, National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration (NOAA), National Oceanographic Data Center (NODC) Working Group, 1997-1998 (Box 182, Folder 2115)
  - US Government, Department of the Interior, Bureau of Reclamation, 1993-1994 (Box 182, Folder 2116)
  - US Government, Department of the Interior, Fish and Wildlife Service, 1983-1984, 1986-1988, 1990-1993, 1996, 1998-1999, 2003 (Box 182, Folder 2117)
  - US Government, Department of the Interior, Geological Service, 1977-1980, 19893, 1991-1992, 1995-2000, 2003 (Box 182, Folder 2118)
  - US Government, Department of the Interior, National Park Service, 1979-1980, 1982, 1984-1989, 1991-1996, 2000, 2002, 2016 (Box 182, Folder 2119)
  - US Government, Department of the Interior, National Park Service, Office of International Affairs, 1976-1977, 1982-1983, 1985-1988, 1990 (Box 182, Folder 2120)
  - US Government, Department of State, 1977, 1980, 1984, 1986, 1991, 1993-1994, 2002-2003 (Box 182, Folder 2121)
  - US Government, Environmental Protection Agency (EPA), 1979-1981, 1986, 1989-1999, 2003 (Box 183, Folder 2122)
  - US Government, Environmental Protection Agency (EPA), Caribbean Office Correspondence, 1979, 1981, 1983, 1991-1992, 1995, 1999, 2003 (Box 183, Folder 2123)
  - US Government, Peace Corps, 1990-1991, 1993-1995 (Box 183, Folder 2124)
  - US Government, US Agency for International Development (AID), Correspondence with Barbados and Other Caribbean Missions, 1977-1997, 2008, 2010 (Box 183, Folder 2125)
  - US Government, US Agency for International Development (AID), Correspondence with Washington, DC Offices, 1979-2000 (Box 183, Folder 2126)
  - US Government, US Agency for International Development (AID), Office of Private and Voluntary Organizations (PVO), 1984-1990 (Box 183, Folder 2127-2028)
  - US Government, US Agency for International Development (AID), Office of Private and Voluntary Organizations (PVO), 1996-2002 (Box 184, Folder 2129)
  - US Government, US Information Agency, 1993, 1995 (Box 184, Folder 2130)
  - University of Florida, Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1972-1982 (Box 184, Folder 2131)
  - University of Guam, 1973-1974, 1977-1978, 1991 (Box 184, Folder 2132)
  - University of Miami, 1972-1974, 1977-1978, 1980, 1982-1983, 1987, 1989, 1993, 1999 (Box 184, Folder 2133)
  - University of Michigan, 1976-1977, 1979, 1983, 1985-1988, 1991, 1998-2000 (Box 184, Folder 2134)
  - University of Rhode Island, 1971-1975, 1977-1982, 1985-1988, 1995, 1998-1999 (Box 184, Folder 2135)
  - University of the Virgin Islands, 1987, 1997-1998, 2001-2010, 2012, 2014 (Box 184, Folder 2136)
  - University of the Virgin Islands, Caribbean Research Institute (CRI), Eastern Caribbean Center (ECC), 1969, 1972, 1993 (Box 184, Folder 2137)
  - University of the Virgin Islands, Virgin Islands Environmental Resources Station (VIERS), 1992, 1994-2000 (Box 184, Folder 2138)
  - University of the West Indies, 1972-1973, 1975-1977, 1980, 1982, 1985-1987, 1989-1999, 2001, 2005 (Box 184, Folder 2139)
  - University of the West Indies, Centre for Resource Management and Environmental Studies (CERMES), 1986-1990, 1994-1995, 2002, 2005 (Box 185, Folder 2140)
  - "V" Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1981, 1986-1987, 1995, 1999 (Box 185, Folder 2141)
  - Virgin Islands National Park, 1977, 1979-1988, 1994-2002 (Box 185, Folder 2142)
  - Virgin Islands Ocean Observing Systems, 2005-2006 (Box 185, Folder 2143)
  - Volk, Richard D., Jr., 1982-1987, 1991-1992, 1994-2000, 2002 (Box 185, Folder 2144)
  - Voluntary Service Overseas (VSO), 1988-1989 (Box 185, Folder 2145)
  - Volunteers in Technical Service Assistance (VITA), 1981 (Box 185, Folder 2146)
  - "W" Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1981-2001, 2005 (Box 185, Folder 2147)
  - Wade, Barry A., 1967, 1969-1970, 1972-1979, 1981 (Box 185, Folder 2148)
  - Water Island, 1998-2000 (Box 185, Folder 2149)
  - Watres, Arthur, 1977-1981, 1984, 1986, 1988, 1992, 1999, 2001 (Box 185, Folder 2150)
  - White Water to Blue Water, 2003-2004 (Box 185, Folder 2152)
  - Widecast, 1986, 1989, 1994, 1998, 2000, 2003-2004 (Box 186, Folder 2153)
  - Wilkinson, Paul F., 1993-1994, 1996-1998 (Box 186, Folder 2154)
  - Woods Hole Oceanographic Institute, 1982, 1985-1987, 1990-1992 (Box 186, Folder 2155)
  - World Bank, 1973-1975, 1977-1978, 1981, 1985-2000, 2011 (Box 186, Folder 2156-2157)
  - World Conservation Monitoring Centre, 1988, 1994, 1996-1998, 2000 (Box 186, Folder 2158)
  - World Resources Institute, 1985-1997, 1999, 2004, 2007, 2011 (Box 186, Folder 2159)
  - World Wide Fund for Nature (WWF) UK, 1990-1991, 1995, 1997-1998 (Box 186, Folder 2160)
  - World Wildlife Fund (WWF), 1972-1976, 1978, 1982, 1984-1991, 1994-1997, 2000-2001, 2005 (Box 186, Folder 2161)
  - World Wildlife Fund (WWF), 1972-1976, 1978, 1982, 1984-1991, 1994-1997, 2000-2001, 2005 (Box 187, Folder 2162)
  - Wright, R. Michael, 1979-19980, 1983-1984, 1986, 1988, 1994-1996, 2001, 2007 (Box 187, Folder 2163)
  - "X, Y, Z" Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1981, 1985-1986, 1988, 1990, 1992, 1994, 1999 (Box 187, Folder 2164)
  - Yale University, 1985-1991, 1993, 1995, 2001 (Box 187, Folder 2165)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1971-1983, 1985-2005, 2007-2008, 2011-2013, 2015-2016 (Box 187, Folder 2166-2168)